喂  你好  乔伊
Hello? Hey Joey!
菲比  帮我个忙好吗
Hey Pheebs! Listen, uh can you do me a favor?
我忘记提款卡的密码了
I forgot the pin number to my ATM card can,
你可以帮我去找吗
can you get it for me?
好啊  在哪里
Sure! Where is it?
我刻在街角的提款机上
Uh, I scratched it on the ATM machine down on the corner.
原来5639是你的密码
Ohh! So you're 5639?!
没错  菲比  谢了
That's it! Thanks Pheebs!
你要跟钱德勒说话吗
Ooh, do you want to talk to Chandler?
是乔伊吗  让我跟他说
Is that Joey?!  Let me talk to him!
不要  他不相信真有电影
No! Because he didn't believe in my movie!
他大错特错  这次的电影是真的
Which is a big mistake because it is real! Real!
我这星期都试着跟他道歉
Y'know what? I have been trying to apologize to him all week!
若他不让我在电话上说
If he's not gonna let me do it on the phone,
我就直接杀过去当面说
I'm gonna go down there and do it in person.
菲比  我听到了  让他听电话
Uhh Pheebs, I heard that. Can you put him on?
好
Yeah!
你别过来
Don't come out here!
不行  我百分之百支持你
No-no-no-no, I've supported you one hundred percent
我要当面证明给你看
and I want to prove that to you in person!
收到  我原谅你  你别过来
I got that! I forgive ya! Don't come out here!
原谅我  你一星期都不接我电话
Forgive me? You haven't been taking my calls in a week!
钱德勒  我早都不介意了
Well, I'm totally over it Chandler.
咱们是一辈子的朋友  你别过来
Friends forever! Don't come out here!
可以跟我们照张相吗
Would you mind doing a picture with us?
什么情况
Uh, what was that?
"今晚娱乐"节目
Uh, Entertainment Tonight.
好了  很高兴跟你说话  你别过来
Yeah, okay so, good talking to ya and don't come out here. All right.
莫妮卡  抱歉我迟到了
Monica! I'm sorry I'm late!
莫妮卡
Monica!
菲比
Phoebe!
菲比  真对不起  你到很久了吗
Oh, Phoebe, I'm so sorry. Have you been here long?
没关系啦
It's okay.
你怎么那么晚
What the hell took you so long?
不许你跟钱德勒说  我遇见了理查德
Okay, you can not tell Chandler. Okay? That I ran into Richard.
哪个理查德
Which Richard?
那个理查德
The Richard.
理查德·西蒙斯  天啊(减重专家)
Richard Simmons?! Oh my God!
不是啦  是我前男友理查德
Noo! My ex-boyfriend Richard!
个子高高有胡子那个
Y'know the tall guy, moustache?
好吧  这就说得过去了  情况如何
Oh! Okay, that actually makes more sense. So how was it?
好极了  我们先是闲聊
It was, it was really nice. We started talking and I-
后来一起吃了个午饭
I ended up having lunch with him.
怪了  我有梦到你跟理查德吃饭
That is so weird! I had a dream that you'd have lunch with Richard.
真的
Really?
不过是跟理查德·西蒙斯啦  你继续说
But again, Richard Simmons. Go on.
奇怪的是  虽然他很棒
The strange part was, he was really nice,
也很帅  但是我对他完全没感觉了
umm and he looks great, but I didn't feel anything at all!
那为什么不能跟钱德勒说
Ooh! So now why can't we tell Chandler?
他听了一定会发神经
Because it would totally freak him out
明天就是我们的周年纪念
and tomorrow's our anniversary.
我不想搞砸
I just don't want anything to spoil that.
不敢相信你们交往一年了
Oh, I can't believe you guys lasted a whole year!
就是
I know.
我欠瑞秋二十块
Wow! I owe Rachel 20 bucks!
什么
What?
那是完全不相干的赌局啦
On a totally different bet.
一周年纪念日快到了
It's almost our anniversary!
我知道  你相信吗
I know. Can you believe it?
一年前的今天  我还只是你烦人的朋友钱德勒
One year ago today I was just your annoying friend Chandler.
现在你只是我的烦人朋友钱德勒
Awww! Now you're just my annoying friend Chandler.
我给你买了礼物
I got you a present!
纪念日明天才到
Oh, but it's not 'til tomorrow!
我知道  但你今天就要拆礼物
I know, but you have to open it today!
好吧
Okay.
我来啦
Okay! There you go!
两张去赌城的机票
It's two tickets to Vegas!
这周末的来回机票
For this weekend!
一定很完美  不但能去看乔伊
Oh gosh, it would be perfect, we get to see Joey
还能在飞机上开始庆祝纪念日
plus we get to start our anniversary celebration on the plane.
就叫做"飞机纪念日"吧
We can call it out plane-aversary.
一定要这样叫吗
Do we have to?
不用
No.
这是很棒  但乔伊说了不要我们过去
Okay this is great, but Joey said he didn't want any of us out there.
他只是怕麻烦我们而已
Oh, he just doesn't want us to go through any trouble.
到时我们突然出现  他一定超兴奋的
Think of how excited he'll be when we go out and surprise him!
而且我们自己还有赌城纪念日
Plus we get to have our own, ani-Vegas-ary!
内华达纪念日
A-Nevadaversary!
我们该开始和别人交往了
Yeah, I think we should see other people.
我们可以去吧
But we can go, right?
-对  -那就好
- Yes. - Okay!
这是个好主意
It's a great idea.
好耶  我也要去
Okay, I'm gonna go too!
菲比  这是我俩的纪念日
Y'know Pheebs, it's kinda our anniversary.
少来  休想像上次伦敦那样把我甩掉
Oh please, you are not gonna ditch again like you did with London.
菲比  哪有甩掉  当时你怀了三胞胎
Ditch you? Phoebe, you were pregnant with the triplets!
真会扯  我非去不可
Uh-huh, great story! I'm going!
注意
Hey, you guys, listen,
这周末大家一起去赌城给乔伊一个惊喜
this weekend we're all gonna go to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
包括我  你们要去吗
Including me!! You wanna go?!
我应该可以请个几天假
Well, I guess I could take a couple days off work.
你当然可以请几天假
Of course you can take a couple days off work
因为这趟我也要去
because this trip includes me!
等等  差点忘了我明天有个推介会
Oh no, wait a minute, wait, I've got a presentation tomorrow.
不能缺席
I can't miss that.
我买了梵高画展的票
Oh, but I've got tickets to the Van Gogh exhibit!
我盼了一年才盼到
I've been waiting like a year for this.
瑞秋  不如我们周六再飞过去
So Rach, maybe you and I can fly out together Saturday.
听起来很可行
That sounds great.
-那我打电话去订票  -好的
- Yeah? All right I'll call the airlines. - Okay.
其实想起来很不赖
Yeah, that would be nice actually,
我可以独自在公寓过一晚
to have the apartment to myself for a night.
对  你可以脱光光到处走
Oh yeah, so you can walk around naked.
不是  我可以自己一个人
No! So I can be by myself. Y'know?
享受下独处的时光
Have a little alone time.
脱光光的独处时光
Naked alone time.
菲比  我一个人独处
No! Phoebe just because I'm alone
并不表示我就想脱光光到处走
doesn't mean I wanna walk around naked.
你自己一个人住  你也不会脱光光到处走啊
I mean, you live alone, you don't walk around naked.
你以为我为何老半天才应门
Uh-huh! Why do you think it takes me so long to answer the door?
迄今为止
So, so far
比起伦敦之行  赌城之行是好还是差
is this trip to Las Vegas better or worse than the trip to London?
菲比  到现在为止都差不多
So it's pretty much the same Pheebs.
那我给你们糖果之后呢
Okay, what about after I give you these candies?
我想好一点了
Yeah, I guess it's a little better now.
好的  赌城1分  伦敦0分
Ah-ha! Okay,  Las Vegas 1, London 0!
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
飞机纪念日快乐
Happy plane-aversary.
我爱你
Aww! I love you!
现在能给你礼物了吗
Can I give you a present now?
-好啊  -好啊
- Okay! - Okay!
要命  不会吧
Oh man! Don't tell me I did this!
我最爱你假装没带礼物了
I love the "I forgot the present" fake out!
那如果我是
How do you feel about the,
真的没带礼物  请你多多包涵呢
"I really did forgot the present, please forgive me" not fake out?
没关系啦
Oh honey that's okay.
别放在心上  等回去再给我就行了
Don't worry about it, you can give it to me when we get back.
纪念日发生这种事  真是再扫兴不过了
Ohh that's the worse thing that can happen on an anniversary ever!
很好
Oh good! All right,
你最后还是决定告诉他理查德的事了
so you decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
什么理查德的事
What-what Richard thing?
糟糕
Oh no.
什么理查德的事
What Richard thing?
用西蒙斯混过去
Simmons! Go with Simmons!
好吧  我昨天遇到了理查德
Okay, I umm, I ran into Richard yesterday
他问我要不要一起吃饭  我答应了
and he asked me if I wanted to go for a bite and I did.
我没跟你说是因为
The only reason I didn't tell you is because
我知道你会生气  我不想毁了周年纪念
I knew you'd get mad and I didn't want to spoil our anniversary.
我不生气啊
I'm not mad.
真的吗
Really?!
真的
Oh yeah!
你遇到理查德  一起吃饭
Yeah, so you-you bumped into Richard! You grabbed a bite!
没啥大不了的
It's no big deal.
太好了
Great!
好吧  伦敦1分
Okay, London 1...
怎么会这样
Oh! Look what happened!
瞧瞧我自己
Huh, check me out!
我在自家的厨房  脱光光
I'm in my kitchen...naked!
拿起一个橙子
I'm picking up an orange.
我脱光光
I'm naked!
点起蜡烛  脱光光
Lighting the candles, naked,
要小心
and carefully.
天啊  瑞秋脱光光了
Oh my God! That's Rachel naked!
不能看  我在看这个
I can't look at that! I am looking at this.
好的  鲜明的色彩  有力的笔触
Okay, vivid colors, expressive brush strokes-
她故意要我看就另当别论了
Unless she wants me to be looking at that.
她知道我在家  她知道我看得到她
She knows I'm home. She knows I can see her.
她这是在玩什么把戏
What kind of game is she playing?
也许今晚有人寂寞了
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
盖勒博士  别胡思乱想
Oh-ho, Dr. Geller! Stop it!
别自讨没趣了
You're being silly!
真是这样吗
Or, am I?
我爱你  小可爱
Love to love ya baby! Ow!
Love to love ya, baby!